CHERYL CAITANO

CONTACT

KAMUELA, HAWAII

(808) 640-4416

cheryl.caitano@gmail.com

https://github.com/ccaitano

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Developer Certificate

University of Washington 2022

Fundamentals of Systems Engineering Certificate

California Institute of Technology 2014

B.S. in Mathematics (Minors in Physics and Astronomy)

Western Washington University 2007 — 2012

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Heroku/Git
- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- MongoDB/Mongoose/SQL
- Progressive Web Applications
- React

SOFT SKILLS

- Bookkeeping
- Collaboration
- Customer Service
- Data Analysis
- Process Automation
- Project Management

PROFILE

Excellent technical, organizational, and time management skills used to streamline processes/procedures and enhance employee productivity and profitability in both small business and large corporation environments. Proven project management, troubleshooting, and team collaboration experience. Strong computer abilities and able to learn quickly and efficiently. Highly adaptable and reliable, requiring minimal guidance.

WORK EXPERIENCE

OFFICE MANAGER

Horizon Automotive, LLC / Kamuela, HI / 2015 - Present

- Receive customers, schedule appointments, delegate technician work statements, and organize/maintain efficient virtual and physical filing systems. Document all processes and procedures. Maintain company website and MSDS records.
- Handle all financial aspects (e.g., account payables/account receivables) including inventory, budgets, payroll services, deposits, and taxation/licensing requirements.
- Create invoices, work orders and estimates. Order applicable parts and manage any customer concerns as needed.
- Scan vehicle computer modules for any current/stored codes and program/reflash vehicle modules using J-2534 equipment.

ADVANCEMENT ASSISTANT

W.M. Keck Observatory / Kamuela, HI / 2016 - 2017

- Process and record all incoming donations.
- Maintain a database of donor information and support the cultivation of donor relations.
- Plan and coordinate all VIP summit tours and dinner events.

TECHNICAL STRESS ANALYST

The Boeing Company / Everett, WA / 2012 - 2016

- Perform complex structural stress analysis for the 787 model interior commodities including passenger seats.
- Act as primary focal for all passenger model Flight Deck Seats analyses, Lean+/5S activities, and the 787-10 model which included developing process improvements, coordinating data transmittals, adhering to strict schedules, and interfacing with internal groups, partners, and suppliers.
- Prioritize the team's work statement, track all team metrics, report status/progress to senior leadership, and program Excel macros and other tools to streamline repetitive team tasks.
- Provide certification plan inputs and coordinate with the Federal Aviation Administration Authorized Representatives and engineers to certify the installation of the interiors for each unique customer configuration.